# Stephen J. Moore

18426 Bittersweet Fraser, MI 48026 (586) 569-6452 <u>stephenmoore@wowway.com</u> www.linkedin.com/in/smoore320

## SUMMARY

Apple-certified repair technician with exceptional communication and technical capabilities. Friendly associate, who excels in fast-paced areas and diverse retail and customer service environments. Specializes in quickly diagnosing and resolving hardware and software-related issues for customers while building and maintaining a strong customer-employee relationship.

#### **HIGHLIGHTS**

- Friendly and outgoing
- Technically knowledgeable
- Reliable and dependable

- Fast Learner
- Cheerful and energetic
- Leader and role model

## **EXPERIENCE**

# Apple - Clinton Township, MI

Technical Expert

October 2017 to Current

- Recently completed experience as Tier 2 phone support working from home.
- Provides fast and efficient technical support to customer's products.
- Perform internal hardware repairs on iPhones in a timely manner.
- Resolve complex systematic, and operating system issues

### Best Buy - Chesterfield, MI

Department Leader (Smart Home Expert)

June 2016 to October 2017

- Performed role play and coached other coworkers based on SOPs or metrics.
- Assisted customers to help them find a full solution to suit their needs.
- Properly sold add-ons like delivery and install services or protection plans.
- Operate POS/order management systems.

# Sears Holdings Corporation - Roseville, MI

Cashier

August 2015 to June 2016

- Coached and performed role-play with underperforming employees.
- Answered product questions with up-to-date knowledge of sales and store promotions.
- Described product to customers and accurately explained details and care of merchandise.
- Monitored cash drawers in multiple checkout stations to ensure adequate cash supply.

# CERTIFICATIONS, AWARDS, ACCOMPLISMENTS

- ACiT iOS Service Certification
- Apple Service Fundamentals Exam
- High School, All "A" Average
- Team Leader Certificate
- Top Sales in District, twice

- "Top Gun" Certificate
- 2<sup>nd</sup> Place in Store Sales
- Employee of the Month
- Employee of the Quarter

### **EDUCATION**

High School Diploma, 2016 - Roseville High School - Roseville, MI